Come on, Shi Ho Ho, let's sing it together
Sadness melts in your mouth and waits for the time to come
In order to polish up the performance to be presented at the new member presentation on April 19
The 10 pinalists attended a two-day and one-night training camp to polish their performance at the new member presentation on April 19.
We closely followed the girls as they struggled and grew.
Our coverage director Iwasaki will bring you the second installment.
Day 2 of the study dayDay 2 of the study day
Second day of study
Day 2 of Study Day 2
Day 2 of Study Day 2 of Study Day 2 of Study Day 2 Let's go a little slower.
You're early.
Singing and dancing is a physical challenge.
It was all I could do to keep up with them.
My muscles were sore the next day.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
We're going without getting in, isn't that too much to ask? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Turn!
Are you okay?
Oh, no! I can't! I can't! I can't! Are the last three of you at the end of your rope? I'm not.
I was running every day for a little bit because of the camp.
I'm going to be a good boy.
I'll be a good boy.
I also did a little running on the riverbed before the camp started.
The one without the track?
It's a riverbed.
The riverbed.
Lemon is solo? Lemon is solo. I already went for a little run on the riverbed before the camp started.
On the riverbed?
Main check
Riverbed
After the early morning run
After breakfast, we started the lesson...
Aaahhhh!
On the second day, we will start with a full-scale singing lesson of the assigned song baton.
We're off to a flying start
We are becoming a big force to be reckoned with
Supported by so many people
Even their kindness
Sometimes we forget or put it away
or put them away.
The treasures you have received
You lick most of them
You can't do anything
You're just dancing around.
Is there a place for Mr. Yamaoka? You can't do anything, you're just thinking.
You can't do anything, you're just thinking.
I'm just thinking about it now.
I think I'm thinking.
I can't do anything, but I'm just thinking.
That's right.
If you have to dance and sing...
I think the physical strength and the way of breathing will probably change.
I think the way of breathing will also change.
I hope I can sing well so that I don't lose my strength in the dance.
I hope I can sing well too, so that I don't lose my strength in dancing.
I hope to sing the last part of the phrase
The longer I stretch the phrase, the more blue my voice becomes.
the longer I stretch out the last part of the phrase, the more blue my voice becomes,
I hear that you are putting it away.
There you are!
Over here.
It's here!
I'm putting it away!
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
I'm often told that I'm a good singer,
I wish I could help you with your singing.
You always start out so well, Hiroshima-san.
I didn't put it in properly.
And the "koronen" part
If you don't get it right
I can't hear "koron-nen ga koro-" if I don't get it right.
I think it would be better if you put it in firmly.
The part where he was falling down earlier is better now. Also, in the Morata Karamon part, if Mr. Hiroshima makes a mistake, Mr. Yamamoto can't enter the part anymore either. And the part about the "given treasure",
When Mr. Hiroshima made a mistake, Mr. Yamamoto couldn't enter it either,
I think there is a phenomenon like that.
Sena Hiroshima had no experience not only in dancing but also in singing,
Sena Hiroshima, who had never danced before, struggled to find the right timing for singing.
A Treasure Received
Overflowing with adults
It's so difficult!
I'm trying to find my way home.
See, what a thing it is to be an overflowing adult, isn't it good? For the sake of this overflowing sound
It's good, isn't it? It's getting better, isn't it?
I'm going to sing while I'm dizzy. It's really good.
I thought all the girls had good qualities, so I was a little surprised at Kuroshima's voice.
I thought she had a nice voice.
Sena-chan's songs can cheer people up, or make them feel better when they watch her delivery,
I was very happy that I could be a source of energy for someone,
I hope to become an idol and be a source of energy for many more people.
On the other hand, what about the A team? On the other hand, the A team?
Look, just this one thing
Even for the sake of overflowingEven for overflowing
I just think
If you laugh while crying, I'm sure you can do it.
I think it's good and Aokawa-san thinks it's very difficult me
The pitch and rhythm are also difficult
me
I don't mean to be rude to my mother, but she is a terrible singer, and I guess I inherited it. But at first I couldn't sing very well, but at the end, my voice lesson teacher praised me that I had improved a lot, and that made me very happy.
Hasegawa-san also struggled with rhythm and pitch. Anyone can do it, anyone can do it, anyone can do it.
Anyone can do it
Neighboring sound
Yes, yes, yes.
I can do it.
I'm not so good at vocals.
When I sing high notes.
I feel like I'm choking
I feel like I'm in a lot of pain.
That's my problem.
I don't know. I'm just plugging it in.
You don't seem very confident.
What do you really think? Is that not true?
I think Mr. Hasegawa and Mr. Sakurai probably have more potential, but I felt that they were not able to bring it out.
Team A seemed to be struggling a lot with singing.
So we decided to do some vocal exercises.
Yoo-hoo, I think we should give it a try!
Shall we do it?
Yoo-hoo!
Yoo-hoo, let's do it
yoo-hoo yoo-hoo, let's try it... yoo-hoo yoo-hoo, let's try it...
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Sai-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta
Sai-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
That'll work, won't it? So...
It's so embarrassing to sing one by one.
I want to be careful to use my breath a lot and make my voice a lot louder.
I want to be careful to make my voice loud.
And Ms. Aokawa, who is having trouble finding the right moment to sing..,
Ms. Aokawa is having trouble finding the right time to sing,
Ms. Aokawa is having a hard time finding the right time to sing,
Mr. Aokawa, who is having a hard time finding the right time to sing, can't sing this song because he is holding back his overflowing fort and no one can do it.
I can't sing!
I can't sing... I can't sing...
I can't sing
I can't sing.
Can you hear the drums? Thank you!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, I hear three drumbeats and then I go in here and it tires.
So, I'm doing it up and down, but it's a little slow.
Oh, yeah.
That's a good feeling if you keep an eye on it.
Don't you know, that's the one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 32, 33, 34, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 40 40, 40, 41, 42, 42, 42, 43, 44, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 47, 48, 48, 50, 50, 50, 51, 52, that's what we're doing.
Don't you think that's that one, 10 years later, 12.
Twelve.
So we're doing it like squeaky clean.
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
What's going on?
Dong dong dong dong.
Even during dance lessons, I tried with the teacher by trial and error
I was trying to overcome my weakness
I wish I could sing with this rhythm
I will do my best
me
I think you've improved a lot. I couldn't do the snow tea lesson because I didn't have to be so attentive to her.
I think you've been doing a good job, but I'd like you to break your color a little bit,
It's not just Rena-chan, though,
I think it would be good if you could be proactive in those situations as well.
That's all I have to say about the performance.
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
Are you all right?
What happened?
It was frustrating.
I thought I had it under control,
I thought I was doing okay, but I knew that I couldn't do what you taught me.
I couldn't do it the way I wanted to.
I don't know.
I felt like I should have done more.
I wish I had done better.
I regret it.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay? Thank you very much.
Rena Sakurai, you've had a lesson that left you with regrets.
But she's going into this audition with a lot of determination.
I think she's been through a lot.
That's why I want to show filial piety.
I wish I could make them happy.
I'm really sorry.
I have two children, and I know it has been hard, but they have given me such a wide range of experiences,
I was given such an important opportunity to participate in the finals,
I want to make it to the finals.
Each of the 10 finalists came to the audition with strong aspirations.
They looked radiant as they earnestly worked on their lessons toward their dreams. 20 years old, she dreamed of singing her songs. She made it her dream to sing her song.
She dreamed of singing her songs.
She dreamed of singing her song.She dreamed of singing her song.
She dreamed of singing her song.
She dreamed of singing her songs. I thought it was a battle with myself, that I would never cut corners to be an idol.
I kept saying I would stop what I couldn't do by 22.
The worst thing I could do was to go public without trying.
I wanted to try everything I could until then.
Pirapo was the one who made me want to be an idol again.
This is the only place where there are a lot of gaps in Zuba.
If it was for Mr. Pirappo
I'm willing to give up all the fun of being a normal girl
I want to be able to go higher and higher.
I want to be better.
We are all rivals.
I want to be the only member who can feel like me. I had a feeling that kindness was coming out of my throat.
If only that one word overflowed
This puzzle will continue
All the way.
Yeah, it's coming together great.
Training camp is finally coming to a close
Both teams are looking good!
Thanks for your hard work at such a place. Good work, guys.
Good work, guys.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please be cold. Haha no - fun!
Fun.
Are you having fun?
The camp is
It's fun.
Don't you miss it?
I miss it.
I remember when we split into two teams.
Yeah.
A team and B team, and we won.
It reminds you of Rio, doesn't it? It reminds me a lot. I also remember the audition for Nijimasu three years ago, when I met the current pure kids.
I love dancing!
I'll cry, I'll cry, I'll cry!
I'm crying, I'm crying, I'm crying
For the prio final
Please do your best!
Thank you so much
Let's stop the consumption tax in my opinion.
LOL!
From Mr. Matsumura, the leader of the group
And a gift for you.
You are a leader who can do it!
Thank you very much.
Cute, cute, cute. Good morning.
So cute!
If it had been one minute longer, I would have cried.
And after this in a hurry, the finalists in front of Piruako.
They're going to show the results of their training camp.
I came to see if you are okay. I'm worried. I'm going to get caught. What should I do?
But I'll just have to enjoy it.
I'm so nervous that I might lose my choreography and singing. What should I do?
What should I do?
♪ I'll dance and sing separately... ♪ Any adult who just wants music can do it, I'm sure.
I'm sure that from the day you reached out to me
When I was dancing and covered in mud, you helped me run toward tomorrow, and I will become a great strength
I'm going to show you the result of my song practice... and it's going to be my great strength as I run toward tomorrow.
I'm supported by so many people, even their kindness, no matter how much I've forgotten
I've put it away.
The treasures I received
I've eaten so much that I'm overflowing
I can't do anything, I just think
But anyone can do it
I'm sure
Just when I was about to fall
And you reached out to me
And from that day on, I wish I could do the same for you.
I've been on a journey to find the next time
And it was turning into strength
When I fell and got covered in mud
The hand that helped me when I was covered in mud
I'm running towards tomorrow
It will become my great strength
I have the support of so many people
Even their kindness
People sometimes forget or put it away
or put it away.
Look, the expensive food
Eating to overflowing
If you can't do anything but think
If you can't do anything but think, anyone can do anything.
Thank you very much.
Everyone's faces looked completely different from the last time we met,
I was very happy to see how hard you were working,
I'm really looking forward to the concert on the 19th,
Please keep up the good work.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
I think that if things continue as they are now, we are all a little bit indefensible,
That's the way it is at this point, so I just want to say one thing, just a little something, like it's okay because you were able to sing the pitch without mistakes or something like that.
It's not like that.
It's not just about getting the pitch right, it's about communicating the feelings of the audience through dance and song.
It's about conveying everyone's feelings through dance and song.
That's what a performance is all about.
As it is now...
I feel like I'm really trying my best to make sure that there are no mistakes.
So, the performance is really about having fun, so I'm really trying my best to make sure that I'm doing the right thing.The truth is, I'm really trying to have more fun, and that's what I'm trying to do, but it's a performance, and as it is now, I'm really trying my best to make sure I don't make any mistakes.
I'm really trying my best to make no mistakes, so I'm really trying to have more fun.
I'm really trying my best to make sure that I'm not mistaken.
will be conveyed through the performance.
I think it will be more wonderful if it is conveyed to the audience and also to the Pilapo members.
I think it will be even more wonderful.
I think it will be even more wonderful if you can convey it to the audience.
I hope you will do your best until the end of the show.
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work.
Okay, well, all the camp reviews will be closed once and for all here, BGM good morning!
Good morning, BGM. Enjoy the show for now.
But the audience still has to pay for the show and buy tickets.
That's all that's left to do.
Don't go on stage without a millimeter of anxiety and confidence.
Don't win in one move without confidence, yes.
I'll be happy if you enjoy the rehearsal and have fun at the show.
Please do.
But there's still time,
Practice once,
I hope you will enjoy singing and performing in the show more than anything else.
I've only seen this team perform once,
I'm super excited.
Sparkling.
No regrets.
I don't care.
The way they sang was great,
Good luck with the 10k or more.
I'm counting on you.
Because today is my true nature,
Do one show today,
I think you can switch off and start working hard tomorrow.
Good luck.
Do your best.
Come on, everyone.
Thank you for your hard work.
Come here, everyone.
Come here.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
So, thank you for the 2 days of training camp. Oh ... Next time, we'll finally go live with the new member presentation.
For 3 months, all I've had to worry about is the audition.
My confidence is about 20%.
We closely followed a day of tension
Let's ask the 10 former members to break the trauma.
I'm going to ask you to do it in a mocking manner.
I'm excited and nervous
I'll do my best with spirit
Fun and excitement, I'll do my best with my spirit